onlinecmag.com 2016-05-09

# .. Privacy Policy .. | OnlineCmag

### .. Privacy Policy ..

We here at OnlineCmag have designed this Privacy Policy page to help you understand what information we collect and use from you and thus helping you choose what you want to share with us.

Note that, by accessing our website ([www.onlinecmag.com](http://www.onlinecmag.com/)) you are accepting the set of practices we follow described herein the Privacy policy.

If you have any queries over the above statement, feel  free to contact us at :  onlinecmag@onlinecmag.com

## **Privacy Policy** :

### **What We Collect From You:**

We at OnlineCmag (company) are the sole owners of all the information collected from you on this Site ([www.onlinecmag.com](http://www.onlinecmag.com/)) . The company collects information in several forms at different instances and locations in the Site. Here are all such areas we collect your information from:

  * **Comments:** Users can choose to leave any comments on the articles they like or dislike. We also entertain our viewers to share information and quieres with us through comments. Commenters can also register anonymously if they choose to.
  * **Mailing List or Subscribers List:** We at OnlineCmag launch a mailing (or) subscriber’s list. This is to provide all our subscribers with information – latest articles, as daily or weekly round-ups.

So as to receive our e-mails users have to register by providing their name and a valid email address. This information will be used by the company only to assess the general user interests, thereby providing users more of what our users want from us. The contact information of any user will not be compromised to any third party.

### **Links To Other Sites:**

The company’s website (www.onlinecmag.com) contains links to several other sites on the internet. Kindly note that OnlineCmag is not responsible for the privacy policies of any such sites. We encourage our viewers to go through the privacy policy of any such sites which request your information.

**Note :  **www.OnlineCmag.com does use cookies to store the visitor’s information.
